{
    "subject": "resource/American_Vacuum_Society",
    "predicate": "ontology/formationYear",
    "object": "1953",
    "human_readable": "The American Vacuum Society was formed in 1953.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8990294337272644,
            "question": "When was the American Vacuum Society formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8234965205192566,
            "question": "Who founded the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7585170865058899,
            "question": "What year did the American Vacuum Society come into existence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6751927733421326,
            "question": "What is the American Vacuum Society known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.539493203163147,
            "question": "What are the main activities of the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4661721885204315,
            "question": "How has the American Vacuum Society contributed to advancements in technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4157581329345703,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of the American Vacuum Society located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3574644923210144,
            "question": "What is the significance of the American Vacuum Society in the scientific community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17013998329639435,
            "question": "Does the American Vacuum Society publish any journals or magazines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.053668055683374405,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing the field of vacuum science today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The American Vacuum Society was formed in 1953.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2860_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the American Vacuum Society publish any journals or magazines?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2860_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of the American Vacuum Society in the scientific community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2860_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the headquarters of the American Vacuum Society located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2860_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2860_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the formation of the American Vacuum Society (AVS) in 1953. For example, both `70.txt` and `23.txt` explicitly mention that AVS was formed in 1953."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}